Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1 MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: 1960 and Before, 1889-1963; 44 Linear feet (44 boxes)
  - Time: 1937: Publishing (Offsite-box 446, Folder 28)
  - Time: 1937: Edit: Style (Offsite-box 446, Folder 29)
  - Time: 1937: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 446, Folder 30)
  - Time: Edit: Ingersoll Prospectus (Offsite-box 446, Folder 31)
  - Time: 1938: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 446, Folder 32-33)
  - Time: 1938: Edit: Style (Offsite-box 447, Folder 1-2)
  - Time: 1938: 15th Anniversary (Offsite-box 447, Folder 3)
  - Time: 1938: Publishing (Offsite-box 447, Folder 4-5)
  - Time: 1938 and Before: Edit: HRL Undated Memos (Offsite-box 447, Folder 6)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Background for War (Offsite-box 447, Folder 7-8)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Reaction to Promotion Book March of Time (Offsite-box 447, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: HRL Marked Copy (Offsite-box 447, Folder 10)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Time The War & Truth (Offsite-box 447, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Jan.-April (Offsite-box 447, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: May-April (Offsite-box 447, Folder 13)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Oct.-Dec. (Offsite-box 447, Folder 14-15)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 447)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Comment [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1939: Publishing (Offsite-box 447)
  - Time: 1939: Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1940: Edit: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 447, Folder 19)
  - Time: 1940: Edit: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 447, Folder 20)
  - Time: 1940: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 447, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1940: Edit: Style (Offsite-box 447, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1940: Publishing (Offsite-box 447, Folder 23)
  - Time: 1940: Edit: Staff Meeting (Offsite-box 447, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1941: Edit: Style (Offsite-box 447, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1941: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 447-448)
  - Time: 1941: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1941: Publishing (Offsite-box 448, Folder 2)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: Air Power Story, 9/42 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 3)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 448)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: Comment [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: Organization (Offsite-box 448)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: Organization [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: World to Come Experiment (Offsite-box 448, Folder 6)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 448, Folder 7)
  - Time: 1942: Publishing (Offsite-box 448, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1943: Edit: Comment (Reports) (Offsite-box 448, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1943: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 448)
  - Time: 1943: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1943: Edit: Organization: Jan.-Aug. (Offsite-box 448, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1943: Edit: Organization: Sept.-Dec. (Offsite-box 448, Folder 12-13)
  - Time: 1943: Publishing (Offsite-box 448, Folder 14)
  - Time: 1943: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 448, Folder 15-16)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 448, Folder 17)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Comment (Reports) (Offsite-box 448, Folder 18)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 448, Folder 19)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Controversy: Foreign News (Offsite-box 448, Folder 20)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 448, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Organization (Offsite-box 448, Folder 22-23)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Style (Offsite-box 448, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1944: Publishing: Mind Power Campaign (Offsite-box 449, Folder 1)
  - Time: 1944: Publishing: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 2)
  - Time: 1945: Edit: Comment (Reports) (Offsite-box 449, Folder 3)
  - Time: 1945: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 4)
  - Time: 1945: Edit: Controversy: Foreign News (Offsite-box 449, Folder 5)
  - Time: 1945: Edit: Organization (Offsite-box 449)
  - Time: 1945: Edit: Organization [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1945: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 7)
  - Time: 1945-1949: Edit: HRL: undated, handwritten memos (Offsite-box 449, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1945: Publishing (Offsite-box 449, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1946: Edit: Style (Offsite-box 449, Folder 10)
  - Time: 1946: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1946: Edit: Organization (Offsite-box 449, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1946: Edit: Boyce Prices Reports (Offsite-box 449, Folder 13)
  - Time: 1946: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 14)
  - Time: 1946: Publishing (Offsite-box 449, Folder 15)
  - Time: 1947: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 16)
  - Time: 1947: Edit: Organization (Offsite-box 449, Folder 17)
  - Time: 1947: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 18)
  - Time: 1947: Publishing (Offsite-box 449, Folder 19)
  - Time: 1948: Anniversary, 25th (Offsite-box 449, Folder 20)
  - Time: 1948: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1947: Edit: Boyce Price's Reports (Offsite-box 449, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1948: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 23)
  - Time: 1948: Publishing (Offsite-box 449, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1949: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1949: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 26)
  - Time: 1949: Edit: Organization: Staff suggestions for improvement: A-M (Offsite-box 449, Folder 27)
  - Time: 1949: Edit: Organization: Staff suggestions for improvement: N-Z (Offsite-box 449, Folder 28)
  - Time: 1949: Edit: Organization: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 29)
  - Time: 1949: Publishing (Offsite-box 449, Folder 30)
  - Time: 1950: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 31)
  - Time: 1950: Edit: Comment: (5/22) Ruth Page Ballet Co. (Offsite-box 449, Folder 32)
  - Time: 1950: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 449, Folder 33)
  - Time: 1950: Edit: Organization (Offsite-box 449, Folder 34)
  - Time: 1950: Edit: They Say Experiment (Offsite-box 449, Folder 35)
  - Time: 1950: Publishing (Offsite-box 449, Folder 36)
  - Time: 1951: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 450, Folder 1)
  - Time: 1951: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 450, Folder 2-3)
  - Time: 1951: Publishing (Offsite-box 450, Folder 4)
  - Time: 1952: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 450, Folder 5)
  - Time: 1952: Edit: Mullen Investment Company (1/21) (Offsite-box 450)
  - Time: 1952: Edit: Mullen Investment Company (1/21) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1952: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 450)
  - Time: 1952: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1952: Publishing (Offsite-box 450, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1953: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 450, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1953: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 450, Folder 10)
  - Time: 1953: Edit: Opinion Experiment (Offsite-box 450, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1953: Publishing (Offsite-box 450, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1954: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 450, Folder 13)
  - Time: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 450, Folder 14)
  - Time: 1954: Publishing (Offsite-box 450, Folder 15)
  - Time: 1955: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 450)
  - Time: 1955: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1955: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 450, Folder 17)
  - Time: Edit: 1955: America (Offsite-box 450, Folder 18)
  - Time: Edit: 1955: Organization (Offsite-box 450)
  - Time: Edit: 1955: Organization [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1955: Publishing (Offsite-box 450, Folder 20)
  - Time: Edit: 1955: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 450, Folder 23-24)
  - Time: 1956: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 450, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1956: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 450, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1956: Publishing (Offsite-box 450, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1957: Edit: Quiz Show Scandal (Offsite-box 450, Folder 26)
  - Time: 1957: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 450, Folder 27)
  - Time: 1957: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 450, Folder 28)
  - Time: 1957: Publishing (Offsite-box 450, Folder 29)
  - Time: 1958: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 450-451)
  - Time: 1958: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 451, Folder 2-3)
  - Time: 1958: Edit: Publishing (Offsite-box 451, Folder 4)
  - Time: 1959: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 451, Folder 5-6)
  - Time: 1959: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 451, Folder 7-8)
  - Time: 1959: Publishing (Offsite-box 451, Folder 9-10)
  - Time: 1960: Edit: Comment (Offsite-box 451, Folder 11-12)
  - Time: 1960: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 451, Folder 13)
  - Time: 1960: Publishing (Offsite-box 451, Folder 14)
  - Time International: 1940 and Before (Offsite-box 451, Folder 15)
  - Time International: 1941: Jan.-March (Offsite-box 451, Folder 16)
  - Time International: 1941: April-Dec. (Offsite-box 451, Folder 17-18)
  - Time International: 1942 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 19)
  - Time International: 1943 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 20-21)
  - Time International: 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 22-23)
  - Time International: 1946-1960 (Offsite-box 451-452)
  - Time-Life Books: 1943-1957 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 2)
  - Time-Life Books: 1958 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 3)
  - Time-Life Books: 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 4)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: 1950 & Before (Offsite-box 452, Folder 5-6)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: 1951-1960 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 7-8)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1923-1936 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 9)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1937-1941 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 10-11)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1942-1946 (Offsite-box 452)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1942-1946 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1947-1950 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 14-15)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1944: Excess Profits Tax (Offsite-box 452, Folder 16)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1951-1954 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 18)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 19)
- Series II: 1961 and Later, 1936-2015; 50 Linear feet (50 boxes)
  - All You (Offsite-box 452, Folder 20)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 452-453)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1971-1989 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 2)
  - Advertising, Corporate (Offsite-box 453, Folder 3-4)
  - Advertising, Corporate: Advertiser's Inserts (Offsite-box 453, Folder 5)
  - Advertising, Corporate: Corporate Campaigns: Before 1964 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 6)
  - Advertising, Corporate: Corporate Campaigns: 1970-1985 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 7)
  - Advertising, Corporate: Corporate Discounts (Offsite-box 453, Folder 8)
  - Advertising, Corporate: Federal Trade Commission Hearing: 1971 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 9)
  - Advertising, Corporate: NYC Advertising Tax: 1971 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 10)
  - America Online: 2002: Washington Post Series: 7/18-7/19 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 11)
  - American Health Corporation (Offsite-box 453)
  - American Health Corporation [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - American Television & Communications (ATC): 1977-1982 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 14-15)
  - American Television & Communications (ATC): 1983-1983 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 16-17)
  - American Television & Communications (ATC): 1987-7/1988 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 18)
  - American Television & Communications (ATC): 8/1988- (Offsite-box 453, Folder 19)
  - American Television & Communications (ATC): Preview Subscription Television, Inc. (Offsite-box 453, Folder 20)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 21-22)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1963 and Later (Offsite-box 454, Folder 1)
  - Asiaweek (Offsite-box 454, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors: 1961-1978 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 3-4)
  - Board of Directors: 1979- (Offsite-box 454, Folder 5-6)
  - Book of the Month Club, Inc. (Offsite-box 454, Folder 7)
  - Books and Arts Associates (Asia) (Offsite-box 454, Folder 8)
  - Books and Arts Associates: Search for Alexander Project (Offsite-box 454, Folder 9)
  - Books and Arts Associates (Offsite-box 454, Folder 10)
  - Books Direct: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 454, Folder 11)
  - Books Group (Offsite-box 454, Folder 12-13)
  - Business 2.0: Edit: 2002- (Offsite-box 454, Folder 14)
  - Cable News Network/CNN (Offsite-box 454, Folder 15)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 16)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 454)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1966-1970 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1971-1989 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 18-19)
  - Civil Defense & Disaster Survival: 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 20)
  - Company Services: Aircraft (Offsite-box 454)
  - Company Services: Aircraft [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Company Services: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 454, Folder 22)
  - Consumer Marketing: 1990 & Later (Offsite-box 454, Folder 23)
  - Cooking Light: Edit & Pub.: 1986- (Offsite-box 454, Folder 24)
  - Copy Processing: 1980- (Offsite-box 454, Folder 25)
  - Corporate Affairs: 1972: Promotion Conference: Nov. 1-3, 1972 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 26)
  - Corporate Affairs: General (Offsite-box 454, Folder 27)
  - Corporate Affairs: Staff Meetings: 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 28)
  - Corporate Affairs: Staff Meetings: 1975-1977 (Offsite-box 454-455)
  - Corporate Communications: 1989- (Offsite-box 455, Folder 2)
  - Corporate Controller (Offsite-box 455, Folder 3)
  - Corporate Development: 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 455, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Development: 1963 (Offsite-box 455, Folder 5)
  - Corporate Development: 1964 (Offsite-box 455)
  - Corporate Development: 1964 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Corporate Development: 1965 (Offsite-box 455)
  - Corporate Development: 1965 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Corporate Development: 1966 (Offsite-box 455, Folder 8-9)
  - Corporate Development: 1967 (Offsite-box 455, Folder 10-11)
  - Corporate Development: 1968 (Offsite-box 455, Folder 12-13)
  - Corporate Development: 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 455, Folder 14-15)
  - Corporate Development: 1971 (Offsite-box 455, Folder 16-17)
  - Corporate Finance (Offsite-box 455, Folder 18)
  - Corporate, General: 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 455, Folder 19)
  - Corporate, General: 1974: Bicentennial (Offsite-box 455, Folder 20)
  - Corporate, General: 1970-1979 (Offsite-box 455)
  - Corporate, General: 1970-1979 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Corporate, General: 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 455-456)
  - Corporate, General: 1987 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 2-3)
  - Corporate, General: 1988 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 4)
  - Corporate, General: 1989 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 5)
  - Corporate, General: 1990 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 6)
  - Corporate, General: 1991 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 7)
  - Corporate, General: 1992 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 8)
  - Corporate, General: 1993 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 9)
  - Corporate, General: 1994: Time, Inc. (Offsite-box 456, Folder 10)
  - Corporate, General: 1994: Time Warner, Inc. (Offsite-box 456, Folder 11)
  - Corporate, General: 1995: Time, Inc. (Offsite-box 456, Folder 12)
  - Corporate, General: 1995: Time Warner Inc. (Offsite-box 456, Folder 13)
  - Corporate, General: 2001- (Offsite-box 456, Folder 14)
  - Corporate Manufacturing & Distribution: 6/30/1961-1969 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 15)
  - Corporate Manufacturing & Distribution: 1970-1987 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 16)
    Name changed after Jan. 1987. See: Magazine Manufacturing & Distribution
  - Corporate Manufacturing & Distribution: Sept. 1976 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 17)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stock: Miscellaneous: 1961- (Offsite-box 456, Folder 18)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stockholders reports to: 1961- (Offsite-box 456, Folder 19)
  - Corporate Secretary: Miscellaneous: 1961 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 20)
  - Corporate Stock: 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 21)
  - Corporate Stock: 1991 (Offsite-box 456, Folder 22-23)
  - Corporate: Time Warner Merger (Offsite-box 457, Folder 1-2)
  - Corporate Stock: 1992- (Offsite-box 457, Folder 3)
  - Cottage Living (Offsite-box 457, Folder 4)
  - Court TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 457, Folder 5)
  - Dialogue Marketing (Offsite-box 457, Folder 6)
  - Discover: Prospectus (Offsite-box 457, Folder 7)
  - Discover: 1979 and Before: Pre-Publication (Offsite-box 457, Folder 8)
  - Discover: 1980: Pre-Publication: Circulation (Offsite-box 457, Folder 9)
  - Discover: 1980: Pre-Publication: Edit (Offsite-box 457, Folder 10)
  - Discover: 1980: Edit (Offsite-box 457, Folder 12)
  - Discover: October 1980: First Issue (Offsite-box 457, Folder 13)
  - Discover: 1980: Circulation: Nov.-Dec. (Offsite-box 457, Folder 14)
  - Discover: 1980: Launch Events (Offsite-box 457, Folder 15)
  - Discover: 1980: Publishing: Sept.-Dec. (Offsite-box 457, Folder 16)
  - Discover: 1981: Edit (Offsite-box 457, Folder 17)
  - Discover: 1981: Publishing: American Renewal (Offsite-box 457, Folder 18)
  - Discover: 1982: Edit (Offsite-box 457, Folder 19)
  - Discover: 1982: Publishing (Offsite-box 457, Folder 20)
  - Discover: 1983: Chinese Edition (Offsite-box 457, Folder 21)
  - Discover: 1983: Edit (Offsite-box 457, Folder 22)
  - Discover: 1984: Edit (Offsite-box 457, Folder 24)
  - Discover: 1984: Publishing (Offsite-box 457, Folder 25)
  - Discover: 1985: Edit (Offsite-box 457, Folder 26)
  - Discover: 1985: Publishing (Offsite-box 457, Folder 27)
  - Discover: 1986-: Edit (Offsite-box 457, Folder 28)
  - Discover: 1986-: Publishing (Offsite-box 457)
  - Discover: 1986-: Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Eastex [empty] (Offsite-box 457, Folder 30)
  - ECompany Now: 2000-: Publication (Offsite-box 457, Folder 31)
  - Edit: 1961: Law (Offsite-box 457, Folder 32)
  - Edit: 1961: Far East (Offsite-box 457, Folder 33)
  - Edit: 1961: America (Offsite-box 457, Folder 34)
  - Edit: 1961: Organization: Newsbureau Recruiting Project (Offsite-box 457, Folder 35)
  - Edit: 1961: Organization: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 457, Folder 36)
  - Edit: 1961: Russia (Offsite-box 457, Folder 37)
  - Edit: 1961: Latin America (Offsite-box 457, Folder 38)
  - Edit: 1961: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 457, Folder 39)
  - Edit: 1962: America (Offsite-box 457, Folder 40)
  - Edit: 1962: Cancer Cigarette Issue (Offsite-box 457, Folder 41)
  - Edit: 1962: Far East: Vietnam (Offsite-box 457, Folder 42)
  - Edit: 1962: Far East: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 457, Folder 43)
  - Edit: 1962: Latin America Including Cuba (Offsite-box 457, Folder 44)
  - Edit: 1962: Organization (Offsite-box 457, Folder 45)
  - Edit: 1962: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 458, Folder 1-2)
  - Edit: 1963: America (Offsite-box 458, Folder 3)
  - Edit: 1963: Cuba (Offsite-box 458, Folder 4)
  - Edit: 1963: Far East (Offsite-box 458, Folder 5)
  - Edit: 1963: Foreign Policy Round Table Life (Offsite-box 458, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1963: Organization (Offsite-box 458, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1963: Russia (Offsite-box 458, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1963: Space Program (Offsite-box 458, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1963: Women (Offsite-box 458, Folder 10)
  - Edit: 1963: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 458, Folder 11-12)
  - Edit: 1964: America: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 458)
  - Edit: 1964: America: Jan.-June [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Edit: 1964: America: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 458, Folder 14-15)
  - Edit: 1964: Editor-In-Chief: Luce/Donovan Transition (Offsite-box 458, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1964: Far East (Offsite-box 458, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1964: Organization (Offsite-box 458, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1964: Russia (Offsite-box 458, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1964: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 458, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1965: America (Offsite-box 458, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1965: Law (Offsite-box 458, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1965: Mideast (Offsite-box 458, Folder 24)
  - Edit: 1965: Organization: Recruitment (Offsite-box 458, Folder 25)
  - Edit: 1965: Organization (Offsite-box 458, Folder 26)
  - Edit: 1965: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 458, Folder 27)
  - Edit: 1966: America (Offsite-box 458, Folder 28)
  - Edit: 1966: Far East (Offsite-box 458-459)
  - Edit: 1/22/1966: Oil Co. President's Luncheon (Offsite-box 459, Folder 2)
  - Edit: 1966: Organization (Offsite-box 459, Folder 3)
  - Edit: 1966: Miscellaneous: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 458, Folder 4)
  - Edit: 1966: Miscellaneous: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 459, Folder 5)
  - Edit: 1967: America (Offsite-box 459, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1967: Far East: Vietnam (Offsite-box 459, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1967: Far East: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 459, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1967: Mideast (Offsite-box 459, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1967: Organization (Offsite-box 459, Folder 10)
  - Edit: 1967: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 459, Folder 11)
  - Edit: 1967-1968: Cancer/Cigarettes (Offsite-box 459, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1968: America: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 459, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1968: America: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 459, Folder 14-15)
  - Edit: 1968: Far East: Vietnam (Offsite-box 459, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1968: Far East: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 459, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1968: Organization (Offsite-box 459, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1968: Russia (Offsite-box 459, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1968: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 459, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1969: America (Offsite-box 459, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1969: Cancer/Cigarettes (Offsite-box 459, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1969: Far East (Offsite-box 459, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1969: Freedom of the Press (Subpoenas) (Offsite-box 459)
  - Edit: 1969: Freedom of the Press (Subpoenas) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Edit: 1969: Organization (Offsite-box 459, Folder 26)
  - Edit: 1970: Freedom of the Press (Subpoenas) (Offsite-box 459)
  - Edit: 1970: Freedom of the Press (Subpoenas) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Edit: 1969: Russia (Offsite-box 459, Folder 28)
  - Edit: 1969: T-L News Service: Fox Hill Inn Conference (Offsite-box 459, Folder 29)
  - Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 459, Folder 30)
  - Edit: 1970: America (Offsite-box 459, Folder 31)
  - Edit: 1970: Far East (Offsite-box 459, Folder 32)
  - Edit: 1970-1971: Forest Industry (Offsite-box 459, Folder 33)
  - Edit: 1970: Miscellaneous: Jan.-March (Offsite-box 459, Folder 34)
  - Edit: 1970: Miscellaneous: April-June (Offsite-box 459)
  - Edit: 1970: Miscellaneous: April-June [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Edit: 1970: Miscellaneous: July-Oct. (Offsite-box 460, Folder 1)
  - Edit: 1970: Miscellaneous: Nov.-Dec. (Offsite-box 460, Folder 2)
  - Edit: 1971: Cancer & Cigarettes (Offsite-box 460, Folder 3)
  - Edit: 1971: America (Offsite-box 460, Folder 4)
  - Edit: 1971: Far East (Offsite-box 460, Folder 5)
  - Edit: 1971: Freedom of the Press (Subpoenas) (Offsite-box 460, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1971: Mid East (Offsite-box 460)
  - Edit: 1971: Mid East [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Edit: 1971: Organization (Offsite-box 460, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1971: Russia (Offsite-box 460, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1971: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 460, Folder 10)
  - Edit: 1973: America: Watergate (Offsite-box 460, Folder 11)
  - Edit: 1972: America: Western Perceptions Seminar (Offsite-box 460, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1972: America: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 460, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1972: Editorial Presentation to Time Inc. Board of Directors (Offsite-box 460, Folder 14)
  - Edit: 1972: Far East (Offsite-box 460, Folder 15)
  - Edit: 1972: Freedom of the Press (Subpoenas) (Offsite-box 460)
  - Edit: 1972: Freedom of the Press (Subpoenas) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Edit: 1972: Organization (Offsite-box 460, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1972: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 460)
  - Edit: 1972: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Edit: 1973: America (Offsite-box 460, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1973: Freedom of the Press: Agnew Subpoenas (Offsite-box 460)
  - Edit: 1973: Freedom of the Press: Agnew Subpoenas [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)
  - Edit: 1974: America: Watergate (Offsite-box 460, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1973: Freedom of the Press (Subpoenas) (Offsite-box 460, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1973: Latin America (Offsite-box 460, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1973: Mid East (Offsite-box 460, Folder 24)
  - Edit: 1973: Organization (Offsite-box 460)
  - Edit: 1973: Organization [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R4)